歡迎喜歡的朋友加入familyguy百度貼吧共同討論
或加FG粉絲交流 QQ群 165859780
□ It seems today that all you see □
□ Is violence in movies and sex on TV □
□ But where are those good old-fashioned values □
□ On which we used to rely? □
□ Lucky there's a family guy □
□ Lucky there's a man who positively can do □
□ All the things that make us □
□ Laugh and cry □
□ He's... a... Fam... ily... Guy! □
□ Family Guy 10x16 □ Killer Queen
殺手女王
片名來自皇后樂隊的同名歌曲
中文字幕: zurica 校對: wudixny 註釋: wudixny
後期: zurica 壓制: zurica @familyguy貼吧字幕組
晚上好 Quahog 我是Tom Tucker
Good evening, Quahog. I'm Tom Tucker.
今晚的頭條新聞：
Our top story tonight:
一件令人震驚的事
In a shocking turn of events,
底特律城被正式放棄了
the city of Detroit has officially given up.
底特律自上世紀60年代起逐漸衰敗
現在前任市長已將城市之匙
The now former mayor has given the key to the city
市長是NBA50大巨星之一的戴夫·賓
交還給了休倫族印第安部落
back to the Huron Indian tribe.
那麼 永別了 底特律
So, farewell, Detroit.
從鮑勃·西格到艾克賽·佛雷 我們壓根兒就不在乎 Joyce
From Bob Seger to Axel Foley, we never really cared. Joyce?
分別是密歇根州搖滾歌手和《比佛利山超級警探》中的角色
謝謝 Tom 本地消息
Thanks, Tom. In local news,
Quahog本週末將迎來一位特殊的客人
Quahog is expecting a special guest this weekend,
著名的亞洲大胃王比賽冠軍
famed Asian competitive eating champion
查爾斯·山本
Charles Yamamoto.
山本至今未輸過一場吃熱狗比賽
Yamamoto has not yet lost a hot dog eating competition
打遍天下無敵手
on his world tour.
不過要是你覺得自己有點本事
But if you think you have what it takes
能夠戰勝世上最厲害的大胃王
to beat the best eater in the world,
請於本週六前往James Woods高中停車場
come down to the James Woods High parking lot this Saturday
帶上50塊報名費 和大胃口吧
with $50 and a large appetite.
哇 也許你應該參加比賽 老爸
Wow, maybe you should enter the contest, Dad.
我敢說你會贏
I'll bet you could win.
好吧 我會的 Chris
Well, I would, Chris,
如果我對自己身材不這麼著迷的話
if I wasn't so obsessed with my figure.
哎對了
Wait a minute.
Chris 你吃過東西了嗎
Chris, have you ever eaten anything?
我就 好像 從來沒停過
Only, like, all the time!
太好了 那我們只需要弄50塊錢
Perfect! Now we just need the 50 bucks.
真該死 我就知道不該為Mort命名那顆星星
Damn it, I knew I shouldn't have named that star for Mort.
有些網站提供收費"命名星星"的服務 多用於送禮或祝願
呃 直接把錢給我算了
Ugh! Just give me the money.
Peter 我們才不會花50塊錢
Peter, we're not spending $50
讓Chris的兩頰塞滿熱狗
so Chris can stuff his face with hot dogs.
好吧 隨你
All right, fine.
我會想辦法自己弄到那筆錢
I'll figure out a way to get the cash myself.
我是個聰明人
I'm a smart guy.
Peter 不 你不是
Peter, no, you're not.
這下你不覺得自己很可笑嗎
Don't you feel ridiculous now?
好吧 Chris 如果我們要支付參賽費
All right, Chris, if we're gonna pay the entry fee
參加大胃王比賽
for that eating contest,
只好賣掉我的一些舊藏貨了
we got to sell some of my old stuff.
- 這些是什麼 老爸 - 哇
- What are these, Dad? - Oh, wow.
我有很久沒看到這些了
I haven't seen those in a while.
這是我珍藏的70年代《花花公子》舊雜誌
Those are my old Playboys from the '70s.
老天啊 真是太性感了
Oh, my God, this one's so hot.
你差不多可以看到一點點女人
You can almost see a little bit of woman.
調侃過去色情雜誌的女優不剃毛
哇 Peter 你有一些很酷的唱片嘛
Wow, Peter, you've got some pretty cool albums here.
是啊 我以前可是個很酷的小肥仔呢
Yeah, well, I was one cool potato back in the day.
要知道 其中有一些可能很值點錢
You know, some of these might actually be worth something.
看這個——披頭士 滾石
Look at this-- Beatles, Rolling Stones.
老天吶 我還從來沒見過這個
Oh, my God, I haven't seen this one in forever.
看看這個 皇后樂隊的"世界新聞"
Look-Look at this. Queen, News of the World.
你看看
Check it out.
啊
Aah!
怎麼了
Oh, what's the matter?
這到底是什麼東西 機器人殺手怪物
What the hell is that?! A killer robot monster?!
不 是"世界新聞"
No, it's News of the World.
是皇后樂隊的一張唱片 看
It's an album by the band Queen. See?
啊 Stewie 別緊張
Aah! Stewie, relax.
不 Brian 把那東西給我拿遠點
No, Brian! You keep that thing away from me!
它…它是不是在看著我
Is it... Is it looking at me?!
它能看到我嗎
Can it see me?!
唉 你還真是害怕這東西 是吧
Man, you're really scared of this thing, huh?
它會吃小男孩嗎
Does it eat little boys?!
我不知道 也許 如果它餓了
I don't know. Maybe, if it's hungry.
給你50塊 這張唱片我買了
Here's 50 bucks. I'm taking this album.
哇 你看吶 Chris
Oh, wow, check it out, Chris!
我們掙到了大胃王參賽費
We got our entry fee for the eating contest!
接下來的五天中
Now for the next five days,
咱倆一門心思只放在訓練上
we're gonna focus on nothing but training.
破曉時分我們就起床
We'll even get up at the crack of dawn.
老爸
Dad?
老爸 該起床了
Dad, it's time to get up.
哎我靠 Chris 天才剛剛亮啊
Oh, jeez, Chris, it's the crack of dawn.
是的 可是老爸 是你讓我叫醒你的
Yeah, but Dad, you said to wake you up.
是的…是的 可是 呃…
Yeah... Yeah, but, uh...
還是…進-進…進來…
Just... get-get... get in...
進被窩裡來 跟你爹媽呆一起
get in the bed with me and your mom.
好的 可是訓練怎麼辦
Okay, but what about training?
哦 你聞著就像融化的奶酪
Oh, you smell like melted cheese.
嘖嘖 嘖嘖 嘖嘖 嘖嘖 嘖嘖 嘖嘖
Yummy, yummy, yummy, yummy, yummy, yummy, yummy.
早上好 Rupert
Good morning, Rupert.
請告訴我你把咖啡機定好時間了
Please tell me you set the timer on the coffeemaker
因為我完全忘了
because I completely forgot.
你這個王八蛋
You son of a bitch!
早上好 看來我幫你起床了
Good morning. Thought I'd help you wake up.
上帝 為什麼他看著很悲傷
God, why does he look sad?!
他已經毀滅人類了啊
He's already destroyed mankind!
他還想要幹什麼
What else could he want?!
嗨 Carl
Hey, Carl.
嗨 能給我拿兩張刮刮樂彩票嗎
Hey, can I get a couple of scratch-off lottery tickets?
當然可以 Brian
Oh, sure, Brian.
唔 Brian 能讓我刮一張嗎 我喜歡刮彩票
Ooh, Brian, can I do one? I love scratchers!
好吧 就刮一張吧
Well, all right, maybe just one.
櫻桃
Cherry.
又一個櫻桃
Another cherry.
嗯 加油 再來一個 再來一個
Oh, come on, one more, one more!
謝了 Carl
Thanks, Carl.
呵呵 不用謝 挺有意思
Yeah, you're welcome. That was fun.
回見
See you later.
哎 謝謝你讓我扮演尤達
Hey, uh, thanks for letting me be Yoda.
星戰版FG中他扮演尤達大師
嗯
Yup.
這是什麼
What is this?
(經典外國兒歌"Pop Goes the Weasel")
呵-呵-呵 我怕什麼呢
Oh-ho-ho, what was I worried about?
啊 啊 啊 上帝啊
Aah! Aah! Aah! Oh, God!
啊 啊
Aah! Aah!
他在流血呢 老兄
He's bleeding, man!
他在流血呢 沒人採取任何措施
He's bleeding, and nobody's doing anything about it!
我來告訴你"世界新聞"是什麼
I'll tell you what the news of the world is.
我們TMD有大麻煩了
We're in a lot of (bleep) trouble!
好的 Chris 就是這兒
All right, Chris, this is it.
這就是我們奮鬥的目標
This is what we've been working for.
如果你感覺緊張 就想像觀眾裸體的場景
If you get nervous, just picture the audience naked
讓熱狗滑進你的喉嚨
and slide those hot dogs down your throat.
女士們先生們 歡迎
Ladies and gentlemen, welcome
來到"世界吃熱狗冠軍大賽"
to the World Hot Dog Eating Championship Competition!
有請我們戰無不勝的冠軍食客
Please welcome our undefeated champion eater,
查爾斯·山本
Charles Yamamoto!
□□ = 怪物
老天吶 那傢伙塊頭真大
Oh, my God, that guy is huge.
好的 食客們 你們有十分鐘時間
All right, eaters, you have ten minutes.
各就各位 預備 開吃
On your marks, get set, eat!
加油 Chris 你做得很棒
Come on, Chris. You're doing great.
繼續保持 你就要成功了
Just keep going. You're almost there.
好吧 我最好抓緊時間了
Well, I'd better get a move on.
時間快到了
Time's almost up!
比賽依然激烈緊張
It's gonna be a close one!
Chris 你還落後四個熱狗
Chris, you're four hot dogs behind!
加油 趕快
Come on! Hurry!
呃 我吃不下去了
Oh! I can't eat anymore.
記得我怎麼跟你說的
Remember what I told you.
我的陰囊邊上長了些奇怪的囊腫
I get these weird cyst things right on the fringe of my sac.
我想去檢查一下
I want to get 'em checked,
但我又怕他們會告訴我什麼恐怖的結果
but I'm afraid of what they're gonna tell me.
他說得對 我能做到
He's right. I can do it!
勝者已經決出
ANNOUNCER: We have a winner!
女士們先生們 山本終於被打敗了
Ladies and gentlemen, Yamamoto has finally been defeated!
Chris 你成功了 你是冠軍
Chris, you did it. You're a champion!
現在你也有了自己的粉絲後援團
And now you get your pick of the groupies.
她們真亮
They're shiny.
是啊 今天挺熱的
Yeah, it's a pretty warm day.
汗津津 O(∩_∩)O
啊
Oh!
嗨 嗨 嗨 你好 冠軍
Hey, hey, hey, there, champ!
啊 看看他 Lois
Aw, look at him, Lois.
大勝之後的小憩
Relaxing after his big victory.
Peter 他不是在休息
Peter, he's not relaxing.
他現在可疼的要命呢
He's in a great deal of pain.
該死 你沒看到自己對他做了什麼嗎
Damn it, don't you see what you did to him?
我跟你說別帶他去參加大胃王比賽
I told you not to take him to that eating competition,
可你卻故意跟我對著干
and you deliberately defied me!
好吧 那你到底想怎樣
All right, what's this really about?
Peter Chris已經超重了
Peter, Chris is already overweight.
我們得為他的健康負起責任來
We need to start taking responsibility for his health.
所以我決定為他報一個減肥訓練營
So I decided to sign him up for fat camp.
什麼 媽媽 我不想去什麼減肥訓練營
What?! Mom, I don't want to go to fat camp!
對不起 寶貝 這都是為了你自己好
I'm sorry, sweetie. It's for your own good.
相信我 你對自己的感覺會變好很多
And trust me, you'll feel much better about yourself.
每個人都想拿我尋開心
Everyone's gonna make fun of me!
唉 不會的 誰要拿你尋開心啊
Oh, come on, who's gonna make fun of you?
嗨 胖墩 我聽說你要去減肥訓練營
Hey, fatty, I hear you're going to fat camp.
那才是你該待的地方
That's where you belong!
Peter 別鬧了
Peter, stop it!
最好別讓我在舞會上看見你
And I'd better not see you at the big dance!
你 走了
Come on, you.
對不起 Chris 我得跟他去了
Sorry, Chris. I-I'm gonna go with him.
嗨 歡迎來到"新開始"訓練營
Hi. Welcome to Camp Fresh Start.
嗯 我們的兒子太肥 所以就來了
Yeah, our son's gross, so here we are.
名叫Griffin
The name's Griffin.
啊 對 Chris Griffin
Ah, yes, Chris Griffin.
我們安排你住在花椰菜小屋中
We have you staying in the Broccoli Cabin.
這麼說你們倆要把我丟在這兒了
So you guys are just gonna leave me here?
是的 寶貝 訓練營就是這樣
Yeah, honey. That's what camp is.
我不想留下來
I don't want to stay!
求你們帶我回家
Please take me home!
我不想參加減肥訓練營
I don't want to go to fat camp!
唉 別啊 Chris 你媽是對的
Aw, come on, Chris. Your mother's right.
這是為你好
This'll be good for you.
呃 那你為什麼不必參加
Well, how come you don't have to go?!
你比我還要胖呢
You're fatter than I am!
哈 問得好 Peter
Huh. Good question, Peter.
為什麼你不必參加
How come you don't have to go?
你們在說什麼
What are you talking about?
呵呵 是你帶他參加了
Well, you're the one who entered him
那個吃熱狗大賽
in that hot dog eating contest.
而且 他說的也對
Besides, he's right.
你自己也好減掉點肥肉了
You could stand to lose a few pounds yourself.
除非你覺得自己做不到
Unless you don't think you could handle it.
哦 是嗎
Oh, yeah?
好吧 我看我能行
Well, I think I can.
你說什麼
What was that?
你別管我說什麼
Never you mind what that was.
起床了 各位
Rise and shine, everyone!
你往裡面藏什麼
What do you got there?
糖塊 是嗎
A candy bar, huh?
還有其他違禁品嗎
Got any other contraband?
- 沒有 - 別跟我撒謊
- No. - Don't lie to me.
我爸曾做過律師
My father was a lawyer.
哦 那你爸就是幫人洗脫罪名的咯
Oh, so your dad gets guys off.
"get off"雙關意為"使人高潮"
Peter Griffin 本屋搞笑大王
Peter Griffin. Cabin clown.
你的包呢 胖子
Where's your bag, fatty?
歡迎你搜查我的"牛肉提箱"
You're welcome to search my "beef case."
諧音"brief case"
但是裡面什麼"羊肉"都沒有
But there's "mutton" in there.
諧音"nothing"
Peter Griffin 本屋搞笑大王
Peter Griffin. Cabin clown.
你麻煩大了 先生
You're in big trouble, mister.
哎喲 這傢伙還真是明察秋毫 不好糊弄
Oh, there's no pulling the wool over this guy's eyes.
看來我得去騎"羊"了
Looks like I'd better go on the "lamb."
也作"on the lam" 意為"躲起來"
Peter Griffin 本屋搞笑大王
Peter Griffin. Cabin clown.
我覺得自己在減肥營中能挺過去
I think I'm gonna do okay here at fat camp.
你確定自己有"排骨"?
You sure you got the "chops" for it?
意為"你確定自己有這能耐"
閉嘴吧你 我才是本屋搞笑大王
Knock it off. I'm the cabin clown.
然後他走進廚房
And then he went into the kitchen,
慢慢打開了冰箱 竟然是空的
slowly opened the refrigerator, and it was empty!
於是 那個人
So then, the man,
餓得全身乏力 從冰箱那裡衝到
weak with hunger, raced from the refrigerator
櫃台前 想找份外賣菜單
to the counter to look for a delivery menu,
但他能找到的全是素菜館
but all he could find was one for a vegan place!
素菜館不是真的 對嗎
Vegan places aren't real, right?
不 他們是假的 還是真的呢
No, they're not real. Or are they?!
啊 沙拉
Aah! Salad!
感謝你的分享 Leonard
Thank you for sharing, Leonard.
我認為其實你買張新沙發才是解決辦法
And I think getting a new couch was the way to go.
誰還有什麼故事
Is there someone else who has a story
要分享嗎 Peter
they'd like to share? Peter?
呃 有 好的
Uh, yeah, sure.
有一次 我乘市內公交
This one time, I was on a city bus,
坐我旁邊的傢伙
and the guy next to me
在吃一桶炸雞
was eating a bucket of fried chicken.
Peter左邊是《美國老爹》中的小胖子Barry Robinson
- 嗯 - 唔 好吃
- Mmm! - Ooh! Yum!
那氣味吸引了我 你們懂的
And the smell was getting to me, you know.
雖然我不認識那個人
And even though I didn't know the guy,
我就埋頭湊上前
I just dug in
開始大口往嘴裡填炸雞
and started stuffing that chicken into my mouth.
嘖嘖 真囧啊
O-Oh! Embarrassing.
我吃過的
I've done that.
太好吃了
It was so delicious.
可…那其實不是炸雞
But... it wasn't fried chicken.
那是個嬰兒
It was a baby!
It was a baby.
惡搞70年代電視劇《風流軍醫俏護士》中最終集的情節
Stewie?
Rupert 我們不會讓那邪惡的機器人
Rupert, we won't give that evil robot
如願以償地殺掉我們
the satisfaction of killing us.
我們要用自己的方式一起上路
We'll go together on our own terms.
另一個世界再見了
See you on the other side.
我的天吶
Oh, my God!
Stewie 不
Stewie, no!
你腦子出什麼毛病了
What the hell's wrong with you?!
因為那個機器人
It's that robot!
他殺了皇后樂隊 現在他也要來殺我
He killed Queen, and now he's going to kill me!
他沒有殺掉皇后樂隊
He didn't kill Queen.
他們都好好活著呢
They're all fine.
大部分好好的
Most of them are fine.
樂隊成員Freddie Mercury1991年死於艾滋病
聽著 Stewie 我很抱歉嚇到了你 好嗎
Look, Stewie, I'm sorry for scaring you, all right?
可不至於吧 那又不是真的機器人
But come on, it's not a real robot.
看 這 這就是張唱片 你看
See? It, It's just an album. Look.
給 你想打它嗎
Here, you want to hit it?
呃…我通常會對那些東西感覺舒服一些
Well... I'm usually more comfortable around things
如果他們能放進我嘴裡的話
if I can put them in my mouth.
那麼 我能把它放嘴裡嗎
So, can I put it in my mouth?
可以吧
I guess.
這就是張唱片啊
This is just an album!
是啊 我已經跟你說了
Yeah, that's what I've been trying to tell you.
那你會原諒我嗎
So, you know, can you forgive me?
唉 我應該會的
Oh, I suppose so.
我是說 連麥哲倫都原諒了那個"陸地喲"的搞怪傢伙
I mean, Magellan forgave the "Land Ho" prankster.
陸地喲
Land ho!
在哪兒 在哪兒
Where?! Where?!
騙你的 傻了吧 擼瑟
Psych! Made you look, loser.
還好沒有陸地
Good thing there wasn't land
不然你就得會見土著人
or else you'd have to meet the natives
- 並穿著這件沾有芥末污漬的上衣了 - 什麼污漬
- with that mustard stain on your shirt. - What stain?
啊
Ah!
唉 我這趟旅程怎麼就帶上你了
Ugh! Why did I even bring you on this trip?!
因為老子是整個歐洲最好的
Because I'm the best damn land spotter
陸地眺望者
in all of Europe.
的確如此 你是最好的
It's true. You are the best.
嗯 我不需要你告訴我這個
Yeah, I don't need you to tell me that.
老爸 我再也走不動了
Dad, I can't take this anymore.
我又累又餓
I'm so tired and I'm so hungry.
我有個主意 Chris 跟我來
I got an idea, Chris. Follow me.
我們要去幹嘛
What are we doing?
我曾經在一本書上見過這樣的樹林
I saw a forest like this in a book one time,
我知道在某個地方有一間姜餅屋
and I know there's a gingerbread house out here somewhere.
出自格林童話"漢斯與格萊特"
你覺得我們能找到它嗎
Do you think we could find it?!
我們必須找到 Chris 我們-我們得吃點東西
We have to, Chris. We-we gotta eat something
不能光靠他們給我們吃的
besides what they're feeding us.
我明白你的意思 老爸
I know what you mean, Dad.
我餓得都能吃下這個死去的訓練營員了
I'm so hungry I could eat this dead camper.
我靠
Holy crap!
好吧 很明顯我們還沒有收集到所有證據
Well, we clearly don't have all the evidence yet,
不過這從沒難倒過我們 對嗎
but that's never stopped us before, right?
哦 這兒沒有其他警察
Oh, there's no other cops here.
不過我們能確認一件事 這孩子是被謀殺的
But we do know one thing, this kid was murdered.
謀殺 這世上有誰
Murdered?! Who in the world
會去謀殺一個營員
would want to kill a camper?
別看我啊
Don't look at me.
我只是送兒子來練練手的
I'm just here to drop off my son.
《黑色星期五》系列中的殺人狂Jason
擁有不死之身 殺露營者(camper)出身
賈斯汀 賈斯汀 那麼做對我不管用
Justin? Justin, that does not work for me.
而且看起來有外傷的痕跡
And it looks like there are signs of trauma
在喉嚨附近
around the throat.
有人勒死了這個胖孩子
Somebody strangled this fat kid.
慢著 他是被勒死的
Wait. He was strangled?
嗯
Yeah.
Joe 我知道是誰幹的了
Joe, I know who did it.
你知道 是誰
You do? Who?
嗯 我知道只有一個人
Well, there's only one person I know
熱衷於勒死胖子：
who likes to strangle fat guys:
Patrick Pewterschmidt.
他是誰
Who's that?
我的大舅子
My brother-in-law.
江湖人稱"胖子扼殺者"
People call him "The Fat Guy Strangler."
見S04E17
他一直對勒死胖人情有獨鍾
He's always had a thing for strangling fat guys.
我看他符合犯罪特徵 Peter
I guess he fits the profile, Peter,
可是Lois的哥哥被關在精神病院啊
but Lois's brother is locked up in an asylum.
好吧 不管怎樣 我們得離開這裡
Well, either way, we gotta get out of here.
不然 我們就成了"坐鴨"
Otherwise, we're just sitting ducks!
"sitting duck"本來指"易受攻擊者"
嗨 我們都知道這傢伙想泡靚妹
Hey, we all know this guy goes for the classy ladies.
惡搞喜劇中心吐槽大會 吐槽者Jeff Ross由本人配音
事實上 我有次碰見他
In fact, I once caught him trying
在勾搭一個妓鴨
to pick up a quack whore.
好吧 別笑了
All right, calm down.
我們都有犯錯的時候
We all make bad choices.
喂
Hello?
Lois 我希望你坐穩了
Lois, I hope you're sitting down.
我有事情要告訴你
I got something to tell ya.
天吶 出什麼事了
Oh, God, what's wrong?
一切都還好嗎 是Chris出事了嗎
Is everything okay? Is it Chris?
不 我是Peter 你老公
No, it's Peter, your husband.
不過我打電話有要緊事說
But I'm calling with big news.
我在訓練營飾演了
I was Anita in the camp production
《西城故事》裡的安妮塔
of West Side Story.
Peter 你知道自己唱快節奏歌曲很糟糕的
Peter, you know you're terrible at patter songs.
我唱得還行呀
I did okay.
□ (mumbles lyrics) ...America □
□ (mumbles) ...America □
□ (mumbling) ...America □
□ (mumbling) ...America. □
我還有另一條消息
I got other news, too.
訓練營有個胖孩子被勒死了
One of the fat kids at camp got strangled!
我的天吶
Oh, my God!
是的 不過別擔心 不是你哥哥干的
Yeah, but don't worry. It ain't your brother.
他還關在精神病院裡
He's still locked up in that asylum.
呃 媽媽…
Um, Mom...
看看誰來拜訪我們了
look who dropped by for a visit.
你好 Lois
Hello, Lois.
Patrick!
好久不見了
It's been a long time.
Peter 他在這兒呢
Peter, he's here!
哎對了 Lois 我想繼續回到
Wait a second, Lois, I want to go back
你說我快歌唱不好的問題上來
to what you said about my patter singing.
你有什麼資格說我
Who gives you the right?!
你知道我演出過《彭贊斯的海盜》
You know I carried Pirates of Penzance
在Quahog社區劇院上映了一季
that season at Quahog Community Theater.
□ 我就是!@#$%^&*將軍 □
□ I am the (sings gibberish) ...general □
□ !@#$%^&*礦 □
□ (sings gibberish) ...mineral □
□ !@#$%^&*歷史 □
□ (sings gibberish) ...historical □
□ !@#$%^&*還有蛋在上面 □
□ (sings gibberish) ...with the eggs on top. □
唉 真希望我們能早點到你家
Man, I hope we get back to your house
趕在Patrick再次行兇之前
before Patrick hurts anyone else!
如果他敢動我家人一根手指頭
If he even lays a finger on my family,
我會像對付"謎語人"那樣收拾他
I'll do to him what I did to the Riddler.
《蝙蝠俠》中的一個反派角色
砰
舔蛋 舔蛋 舔蛋 舔蛋
不許動 瘋子
Freeze, psycho!
哦 Peter 謝天謝地
Oh, Peter, thank God!
Patrick Pewterschmidt 你被逮捕了
Patrick Pewterschmidt, you're under arrest
你涉嫌謀殺 呃…
for the murder of, uh... (bleep)
我不知道那孩子叫什麼
I didn't get the kid's name.
我們真應該弄清楚
We're supposed to do that.
Lois 你叫警察來的
Lois, you called the cops?
Patrick 你是我哥哥 我愛你 但你不是好人
Patrick, you're my brother and I love you, but you're not well.
可我現在好多了
But I'm better now.
我已經跟過去決裂了
I've put my past behind me.
省省吧 Patrick
Save it, Patrick.
我們都知道你從精神病院逃出 殺了…
We know you escaped from the asylum and killed...
Bill 我們現在用"Bill"來指代他
Bill, we'll just call him "Bill" for now.
逃出 我-我沒有逃啊
Escaped? I-I didn't escape.
就在今天上午 一位很友善的先生打開了我房間的門
Just this morning, a very nice gentleman opened my cell door
說我可以自由離開了
and said I was free to go.
呵 編的真好 不過沒用
Yeah, nice try. That's not how it works.
Patrick舅舅 為什麼你要勒死胖人
Uncle Patrick, why do you strangle fat people?
大概是奇怪的戀物癖行為
It's probably a weird fetish thing.
有些罪犯是這樣的
Some criminals have 'em.
比如那些過分講究細節的劫匪
Like those anal-retentive bandits
他們去年搶劫了Quahog銀行
who robbed Quahog Bank last year.
聽好了 舉起手來 舉直了
All right, hands in the air! Vertically!
兩隻胳膊必須互相平行
Both arms should be parallel to each other!
你 把這個袋子裡裝滿乾淨的 無記號的鈔票
You, fill this bag with clean, unmarked bills!
不過首先把那個記事本放好 這樣它才能跟
But first fix that notepad so it's at a right angle
你的桌角呈正確的角度
with the corner of your desk!
在桌面上整一整那摞收條
And tap that pile of receipts against a flat surface
這樣它們看起來才不會參差不齊
so they're not sticking out haphazardly!
還是這樣吧 先別想什麼錢了
You know what?! Forget about the money!
每個人都去拿一把掃帚
Everybody grab a broom!
我們把這地方好好收拾一番
We are straightening this place up!
好的 營員們
All right, campers,
在胖子扼殺者被抓到之前
until the Fat Guy Strangler is caught,
每個人都得呆在自己屋裡
everyone has to stay inside their cabins.
現在我要清點一下人數
Now I'm gonna do a stomach count.
當我叫到你的名字 請回答
When I call your name, please respond.
Jenkins?
Robertson?
Davis?
Elliot?
Elliot上哪兒去了
Where's Elliot?
我看他在睡覺吧
I think he's asleep.
Elliot Elliot 醒醒
Elliot? Elliot, wake up.
Elliot?
我是Swanson警官
Officer Swanson here.
什麼 我的天吶
What?! Oh, my God!
怎麼了 Joe
What is it, Joe?
半小時前又一個營員被勒死了
Another camper was strangled half an hour ago.
可…也就是說…
But... that means...
Patrick不可能是兇手
Patrick can't be the killer.
我就是這麼跟你們說的嘛
That's what I was trying to tell you.
收到了 我正在處理
Acknowledged. I'm on it.
Joe 你願意為營裡解決一個爭端嗎
Joe, would you settle a camp argument?
是"轟炸球"好 還是"躲避球"好
Is it "Bombardment" or "Dodgeball"?
"轟炸球"是躲避球的升級版 有三種不同的球
躲避球
Dodgeball.
啊 你還是不懂
Ah, you don't know.
好吧 我還是發佈全境通告
Well, I'd better put out an APB
到附近的各個城鎮
to all the neighboring towns.
呃 殺手不會離開減肥營的
Oh, the murderer won't leave the camp.
什麼 你剛才說什麼
What? What are you talking about?
他在"進食"
He's "feeding."
他殺了兩個人 而且會再殺人
He killed twice and he's gonna do it again.
他在那兒有許多地方可以藏身
He's got plenty of places to hide out there
也有數量充足受害者可以下手
and a fully stocked corral of victims.
你怎麼知道
How do you know that?
相信我 我懂的
Trust me. I know.
其實 Joe 說不定Patrick真能幫上忙
You know, Joe, maybe Patrick can actually be of help.
我是說 還有誰更瞭解那人的想法
I mean, who better to get inside the mind of someone
除非他自己也勒死過胖子 不然怎麼想得到
who's strangling fat people than someone who's done it himself?
是啊 給他個機會吧 Joe
Yeah, give him a chance, Joe.
就像我對非主流少年那樣
Like I did with scary teenagers.
我曾經很害怕他們 直到我意識到
I used to be afraid of 'em, until I realized
他們只是被誤解了
they were just misunderstood.
嗨 死胖子 把你錢包給我
Hey, fat ass, give me your wallet!
我可以給你錢包
I could give you my wallet,
不過我覺得你真正想要的…
but what I think you really want...
是愛
is love.
是真的
It's true!
我要拿走你的鞋
I'm taking your shoes.
可憐的孩子
Poor kid.
其實 最詭異的是
You know, the weirdest thing is
他的床鋪很靠近Chris的
his bunk is right next to Chris's.
是啊 還真是僥倖啊
Yeah, that was a close call.
哦 這可不僅是僥倖的問題
Oh, it was more than a close call.
你說過第一個受害者戴著棒球帽
You said the first victim was wearing a baseball cap,
第二個受害者是金髮…
this second one is blond...
殺手並不是想殺這個孩子
The killer wasn't trying to murder this kid.
他是想殺Chris
He was trying to murder Chris.
我的天吶
Oh, my God!
為什麼有人會想殺Chris
W-Why would anyone want to kill Chris?
我不知道 不過我知道
I don't know, but I do know
他現在的處境十分危險
that he's in a great deal of danger right now.
- 快點 咱們走 - 好的
- Come on. Let's go! - Yeah!
不過稍等 這是咱們最後的機會來玩"搶內褲"遊戲了
But wait, this is our last chance to do a panty raid!
哎 減肥營 我們成功了
Yay! Fat camp! We got it!
哦 不 一陣強風
Oh, no, a gust of wind!
你 你在這兒幹什麼
Wha, what are you doing here?
你讓我顏面盡失 Chris Griffin
You dishonored me, Chris Griffin.
沒有人可以比我吃更多的熱狗
No one has ever eaten more hot dogs than me.
現在你必須去死
Now you must die!
STEWIE：喂 死胖子
STEWIE: Hey, fat ass!
我有好消息(新聞)要告訴你
I got news for you.
世界新聞
The News of the World!
為什麼機器人捧著死人
Why does robot hold dead people?!
那是未來還是過去
Is that future or past?!
老天吶 Stewie 你救了我的命
Oh, my God, Stewie, you saved my life!
啊 你也會為我做同樣的事 Chris
Ah, you would've done the same for me, Chris.
關鍵是 我們都平安無事
The important thing is, we're all gonna be okay.
對嗎 大機器人
Right, Giant Robot?
查爾斯·山本…從大胃王冠軍
Charles Yamamoto... went from eating champion
變成了冷血殺手
to cold-blooded killer.
誰能想到呢
Who'd have thought?
哦對了 Joe 他就是昨天
Wait a minute, Joe. That's the guy who opened
替我開門 告訴我
the door to my cell yesterday and told me
可以離開精神病院的人
I could leave the asylum.
哈 是那樣嗎
Huh. Is that right?
好吧 那一切都說得通了
Well, then it all makes sense.
山本想讓這事看起來
Yamamoto wanted it to look like
像你自己出逃造成的
you broke out on your own.
那樣的話 當他謀殺了Chris
That way, when he murdered Chris,
就必然由你來當替罪羊了
it was a cinch that you would take the blame.
好吧 Patrick 看來我們欠你一個道歉
Well, Patrick, I guess we all owe you an apology.
Patrick?
他去哪兒了
Where did he go?
他剛才還在這兒的
He was just right here.
發生什麼了
What happened?!
該死 他肯定已經逃跑了
Damn it! He must've gotten away!
這怎麼可能呢
How is that possible?!
我不知道 不過我最好弄成
I don't know, but I'd better make it
搏鬥過的樣子
look like there was a struggle.
誰向我臉上打一拳
Someone punch me in the face.
我可是你的好朋友呢
I'm a good friend to you.
中文字幕: zurica 校對: wudixny 註釋: wudixny
後期: zurica 壓制: zurica @familyguy貼吧字幕組
皇后樂隊的"Killer Queen"